{
    "subject": "resource/Eddie_Peng",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Taipei",
    "human_readable": "Eddie Peng was born in Taipei.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8331994414329529,
            "question": "Where was Eddie Peng born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216472864151001,
            "question": "Is Eddie Peng still living in Taipei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8042513132095337,
            "question": "Name the city where Eddie Peng was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761229932308197,
            "question": "In what year was Eddie Peng born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5635164380073547,
            "question": "What is Eddie Peng's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.444726824760437,
            "question": "What is Eddie Peng known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22997072339057922,
            "question": "Does Eddie Peng speak any languages besides Mandarin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1690651774406433,
            "question": "What type of roles does Eddie Peng typically play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15618553757667542,
            "question": "Has Eddie Peng worked in any film productions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15442496538162231,
            "question": "Has Eddie Peng won any awards for his acting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eddie Peng was born in Taipei.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8463_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Eddie Peng worked in any film productions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8463_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles does Eddie Peng typically play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8463_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Eddie Peng speak any languages besides Mandarin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8463_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8463_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe triple statement \"Eddie Peng was born in Taipei\" can be found in multiple documents, specifically in file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8463/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8463/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt, where it is mentioned that Eddie Peng was born in Taipei, also known as Peng Yu-yen. Additionally, in file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8463/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8463/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt, it is mentioned that Eddie Peng was born in Taiwan Taipei or Taiwan respectively, which supports the statement that he was indeed born in an area now known as Taipei."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Eddie Peng (\u5f6d\u4e8e\u664f) was born on March 24, 1982, in Taipei, Taiwan. Therefore, the statement \"Eddie Peng was born in Taipei\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}